A Guide to the JMU Sports Posters Collection, 1976-2000
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Special Collections, James Madison University
JMU Sports Posters Collection1976-2000
Special Collections, James Madison University
5033
1 flat box
The JMU Sports Posters collection contains posters, mainly from the 1990s, advertising sports events for that school year, as well as an advertising poster for the James Madison University Recreational (UREC) facility
JMU Photography Service
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Michael Miriello the new JMU photographer transferred this collection from the Athletic Department in Chandler Hall.
Historical Information
Posters were used to distribute the schedule of JMU sports events, as well as raise awareness of the JMU sports programs
Scope and Content
The JMU Sports Posters collection contains posters, mainly from the 1990s, advertising sports events for that school year, as well as an advertising poster for the JMU UREC facility.
Series I – Football Posters contains posters which both advertise the JMU Football team and distribute their schedule of athletic events for a given academic year.
Series II – Men’s Basketball Posters contains posters which both advertise the JMU Men’s Basketball and distribute their schedule of athletic events for a given academic year.
Series III – Women’s Basketball Posters contains posters which both advertise the JMU Women’s Basketball team and distribute their schedule of athletic events for a given academic year.
Series IV – Men’s Soccer Posters contains posters which both advertise the JMU Men’s Soccer team and distribute their schedule of athletic events for a given academic year.
Series V – Women’s Soccer Posters contains posters which both advertise the JMU Women’s Soccer team and distribute their schedule of athletic events for a given academic year.
Series VI – Baseball Posters contains posters which both advertise the JMU Baseball team and distribute their schedule of events for a given academic year.
Series VII- UREC Posters contains posters which advertise the JMU UREC facility.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series:
I: Football Posters
II: Men’s Basketball Posters
III: Women’s Basketball Posters
IV: Men’s Soccer Posters
V: Women’s Soccer Posters
VI: Baseball Posters
VII: UREC Posters
Contents List
- Football Posters
  - 1986 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - 1989 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - 1990 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - 1991 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - 1991 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - 1994 (Box-folder 1:6)
- Men's Basketball Posters
  - 1976-1977 (Box-folder 1:7)
  - 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1:9)
  - 1990-1991 (Box-folder 1:10)
  - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1:11)
  - 1992-1993 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1:13)
  - 1995-1996 (Box-folder 1:14)
  - 1997-1998 (Box-folder 1:15)
  - 1998-1999 (Box-folder 1:16)
  - 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1:17)
- Women's Basketball Posters
  - 1985-1986 (Box-folder 1:18)
  - 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1:19)
  - 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1:20)
  - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1:21)
  - 1992-1993 (Box-folder 1:22)
  - 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1:23)
  - 1994-1995 (Box-folder 1:24)
  - 1995-1996 (Box-folder 1:25)
  - 1996-1997 (Box-folder 1:26)
  - 1997-1998 (Box-folder 1:27)
  - 1998-1999 (Box-folder 1:28)
  - 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1:29)
- Men's Soccer Posters
  - 1991 (Box-folder 1:30)
  - 1994 (Box-folder 1:31)
  - 1996 (Box-folder 1:32)
- Women's Soccer Posters
  - 1997 (Box-folder 1:33)
  - 1998 (Box-folder 1:34)
  - 1999 (Box-folder 1:35)
- Baseball Posters
  - 1997 (Box-folder 1:36)
  - 1998 (Box-folder 1:37)
- UREC Posters
  - Undated (Box-folder 1:38)